**Alternate Mobile No.**: +91 9146504731

Email ID: neha16595@gmail.com

#### > SYNOPSIS

4 years of IT experience in Functional Testing and Non-Functional Testing – Automation (Selenium WebDriver), Manual & Quality Assurance. Seeking a challenging and exciting career where currency are ideas, smart work with rigorous thinking and boundless curiosity.

### > AREAS of EXPERTISE

E2E Manual Testing - Web applications,     Mobile App Testing	<ul> <li>Automation – Web Applications (Selenium WebDriver)</li> </ul>
Test Data Preparation – Web / Mobile	Test / Defect reporting and management

#### > TECHNICAL SKILLS

Tools	Selenium WebDriver, PyCharm, Bitbucket, Bitrise
Other Tools	Eclipse, Jira, qTest
Frameworks	TestNG, Data Driven Development, Page Object Model
Languages known	Java, SQL
Functional Area	Core Banking, Retail Banking
Operating System	Windows / iOS / Android

# **EDUCATION**

**Bachelor of Engineering in Information Technology** 

University – North Maharashtra University, Jalgaon (MH)

College - R. C. Patel Institute of Technology, Shirpur (MH)

Percentage - 62.90 % in year 2017

**Alternate Mobile No.**: +91 9146504731

Email ID: neha16595@gmail.com

# > CERTIFICATION SUMMARY

• Completed Selenium Advanced Automation Tester Certification (Infosys Limited)

• Diploma in Software Testing (SEED InfoTech)

# **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

Infosys Limited, Pune Designation: Test Engineer LWD – 9 <sup>th</sup> May, 2022		
Current Project: Ally I	Bank – Banking domain (Apr 2021 – till date)	
Technology Stack	Manual Testing, Mobile Automation (PyCharm), Jira, qTest	
Responsibilities	<ul> <li>Execute test cases manually at the time of Regression Testing</li> <li>Test case management using qTest</li> <li>Identify candidate for automation Testcases and develop the test scripts.</li> <li>Used Bitrise platform to manage application binaries</li> <li>Executed the Test suite run on automation suites in BrowserStack</li> <li>Automated test scripts for different platforms like iOS, Android</li> <li>Defect Reporting and tracking using Jira</li> <li>Contributed into other teams for UI validation</li> </ul>	

INNsight Interactive, Mumbai Designation: QA Analyst		
Previous Project: Ho	spitality domain project (Sep 2019 – Apr 2021)	
Technology Stack	Manual Testing, Selenium, Java, Web Automation	
Responsibilities	<ul> <li>Analyzed Business and Functional Requirement specifications</li> <li>Identify and write the test cases in excel</li> <li>Manual Test case execution on web and mobile application</li> <li>Performed Cross browser Testing</li> <li>Automated test scripts for Web application and websites, using Selenium WebDriver</li> <li>Defect Reporting and Defect tracking using Jira</li> </ul>	

**Alternate Mobile No.**: +91 9146504731

Email ID: neha16595@gmail.com

Xinet Technologies Pvt. Ltd., Nashik Designation: QA Engineer		
Previous Project: Seller Overview (Dec 2017 – Aug 2019)		
Technology Stack	Manual Testing, Jira	
Responsibilities:	<ul> <li>Analyzed Business and Functional Requirement Specification</li> <li>Identify and write the test scenarios and test cases in Excel.</li> <li>Performed Functional and non-functional testing</li> <li>Worked on Web Application aspects and UI Testing</li> <li>Defect Reporting and Defect Verification</li> </ul>	

Xinet Technologies Pvt. Ltd., Nashik Designation: QA Engineer		
Previous Project: Somers Crossing (Dec 2017 – Aug 2019)		
Technology Stack	Manual testing, Jira	
Responsibilities:	<ul> <li>Analyzed Business and Functional Requirement Specification</li> <li>Identify and write the test scenarios and test cases in Excel.</li> <li>Execute test cases manually</li> <li>Defect Reporting and Defect Verification.</li> </ul>	

**Alternate Mobile No.**: +91 9146504731

Email ID: neha16595@gmail.com

### > STRENGTHS

- Capable of Quick learning and delivering solutions as an individual and as part of a team
- Good analytical skills, presentation skills with good communication skills
- self-starter and consistent performer
- Result oriented, self-driven, highly motivated, smart, and hungry to learn new technologies, methodologies, strategies, and processes.

#### > PERSONAL INFORMATION

Marital Status: Unmarried
 Hobbies: Singing, Dancing
 Date of birth: 16<sup>th</sup> May 1995

• Permanent address: Khanderao Pada, Thalner, Tal. Shirpur, Dist. Dhule, 425421